=== GOVERNOR LOOP RUN 006 ù THE SCALE PARADOX ===
Model: gpt-4o-mini
Prior attractors (M7): ['FT&E reveals patterns in chaos through flexible interpretation.', 'FT&E supports adaptive navigation through complexity by independently assessing forgiveness, time, and contradiction load.', 'Local insights enrich global understanding.']


=== RESULT ===
Contradiction class:  C3_FOUNDATIONAL
Emergence ready:      True
New attractor:        Localized validation enhances universal principles through iterative refinement, fostering a feedback loop that respects individual insights while remaining adaptable to collective understanding.
Core phrase:          Growth emerges through iterative refinement of local insights into adaptable universal truths.
Anchor symbol:        The Spiral
Stability index:      0.6499999999999999
E* score:             0.594
F score:              0.7
T elapsed (s):        19.911
Delta C:              0.8
Failure mode:         none
